League for Industrial Democracy Pamphlets 5266
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- L [folder 7 of 7], Publication (Box 1, Folder 12g)
  - Item 82: Looking Forward: Discussion Outlines, Publication (Box 1, Folder 12g)
  - Item 83: Looking Forward: Discussion Outlines, Publication (Box 1, Folder 12g)
  - Item 84: Looking Forward: Discussion Outlines, Publication (Box 1, Folder 12g)
  - Item 85: Looking Forward: Discussion Outlines, Publication (Box 1, Folder 12g)
  - Item 86: Looking Forward: Discussion Outlines, Publication (Box 1, Folder 12g)
  - Item 87: Looking Forward: Discussion Outlines, Publication (Box 1, Folder 12g)
  - Item 88: Looking Forward: Discussion Outlines, Publication (Box 1, Folder 12g)
  - Item 89: Correspondence, Publication (Box 1, Folder 12g)
  - Item 90: How America Lives: A Handbook of Industrial Facts, Publication (Box 1, Folder 12g)
  - Item 91: Forty-Five Years of Social Education, Publication (Box 1, Folder 12g)
  - Item 92: Postwar Planning for Peace and Full Employment, Publication (Box 1, Folder 12g)
- Mc, Publication (Box 1, Folder 13)
  Empty
- M, Publication (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Item 1: The Intelligent Consumers Guide to Hospital and Medical Plans, Publication (Box 1, Folder 14)
    By Harold Maslow. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Facism, Publication (Box 1, Folder 14)
    By J. B. Matthews; R. E. Shallcross. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: Traffic in Death, Publication (Box 1, Folder 14)
    By J. B. Matthews. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: Southern Labor In Revolt, Publication (Box 1, Folder 14)
    By Kenneth Meiklejohn; Peter Nehemkis. Item is in English.
  - Item 5: Socialism's New Beginning: a manifesto from underground Germany, Publication (Box 1, Folder 14)
    By Miles; H. N. Brailsford; Norman Thomas. Item is in English.
  - Item 6: Does Norwegian Labor Seek the Middle Way, Publication (Box 1, Folder 14)
    By Finn Moe. Item is in English.
  - Item 7: The Automobile Industry and Organized Labor, Publication (Box 1, Folder 14)
    By A. J. Muste. Item is in English.
  - Item 8: The British Health Service, Publication (Box 1, Folder 14)
    By Julius Manson. Item is in English.
  - Item 9: The British Health Service, Publication (Box 1, Folder 14)
    By Julius Manson. Copy 2. Item is in English.
  - Item 10: Does Norwegian Labor Seek the Middle Way, Publication (Box 1, Folder 14)
    By Finn Moe. Copy 2. Item is in English.
  - Item 11: The Intelligent Consumers Guide to Hospital and Medical Plans, Publication (Box 1, Folder 14)
    By Harold Maslow. Copy 2. Item is in English.
- N, Publication (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Item 1: Irrepressible America, Publication (Box 1, Folder 15)
    By Scott Nearing. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: European Trade Unionism and Politics, Publication (Box 1, Folder 15)
    By Franz Neumann. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: European Trade Unionism and Politics, Publication (Box 1, Folder 15)
    By Franz Neumann. Copy 2. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: European Trade Unionism and Politics, Publication (Box 1, Folder 15)
    By Franz Neumann. Copy 3. Item is in English.
- O, Publication (Box 1, Folder 16)
- P, Publication (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Item 1: The Office Worker Labors Side of the Ledger, Publication (Box 1, Folder 17)
    By Orlie Pell. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: The Office Worker Labors Side of the Ledger, Publication (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Item 3: What Price Telephones?, Publication (Box 1, Folder 17)
    By Norman Perelman. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: We Dont Help Blacks by Hurting Whites, Publication (Box 1, Folder 17)
    By Nathan Pearlmutter. Item is in English.
  - Item 5: The Office Worker Labors Side of the Ledger, Publication (Box 1, Folder 17)
    By Orlie Pell. Copy 2. Item is in English.
  - Item 6: The Office Worker Labors Side of the Ledger, Publication (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Item 7: The Office Worker Labors Side of the Ledger, Publication (Box 1, Folder 17)
    By Orlie Pell. Copy 3. Item is in English.
  - Item 8: What Price Telephones?, Publication (Box 1, Folder 17)
    By Norman Perelman. Copy 2. Item is in English.
  - Item 9: The Office Worker Labors Side of the Ledger, Publication (Box 1, Folder 17)
- Q, Publication (Box 1, Folder 18)
- R, Publication (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Item 1: Fordism, Publication (Box 1, Folder 19)
    By Carl Raushenbush. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: The Peoples Fight for Coal and Power, Publication (Box 1, Folder 19)
    By H. S. Raushenbush. Item is in English.
- S [folder 1 of 2], Publication (Box 1, Folder 20a)
  - Item 1: Anti-Labor Activities in the United States, Publication (Box 1, Folder 20a)
    By David J. Saposs; Elizabeth T. Bliss. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Sit-down; A. G. M. Stockholder Visits Flint, Publication (Box 1, Folder 20a)
    By Joel Seidman; Robert Morss Flint. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: Shall Strikes Be Outlawed?, Publication (Box 1, Folder 20a)
    By Joel Seidman. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: Mexico In Transition, Publication (Box 1, Folder 20a)
    By Clarence Senior. Item is in English.
  - Item 5: What Is FolkSocialism? A Critical Analysis, Publication (Box 1, Folder 20a)
    By Paul Sering. Item is in English.
  - Item 6: The Intellectual And The Labor Movement, Publication (Box 1, Folder 20a)
    By George Soule. Item is in English.
  - Item 7: The Accumulation of Capital: Social vs. Personal Savings, Publication (Box 1, Folder 20a)
  - Item 8: Labor Looks at Education, Publication (Box 1, Folder 20a)
    By Mark Starr. Item is in English.
  - Item 9: Workers Education Today, Publication (Box 1, Folder 20a)
  - Item 10: New Zealands Labor Government at Work, Publication (Box 1, Folder 20a)
    By W. B. Sutch. Item is in English.
  - Item 11: Anti-Labor Activities in the United States, Publication (Box 1, Folder 20a)
    By David J. Saposs; Elizabeth T. Bliss. Copy 2. Item is in English.
  - Item 12: Anti-Labor Activities in the United States, Publication (Box 1, Folder 20a)
    By David J. Saposs; Elizabeth T. Bliss. Copy 3. Item is in English.
  - Item 13: Sit-down; A. G. M. Stockholder Visits Flint, Publication (Box 1, Folder 20a)
    By Joel Seidman; Robert Morss Flint. Copy 2. Item is in English.
  - Item 14: Shall Strikes Be Outlawed?, Publication (Box 1, Folder 20a)
    By Joel Seidman. Copy 2. Item is in English.
  - Item 15: Shall Strikes Be Outlawed?, Publication (Box 1, Folder 20a)
    By Joel Seidman. Copy 3. Item is in English.
  - Item 16: What Is FolkSocialism? A Critical Analysis, Publication (Box 1, Folder 20a)
    By Paul Sering. Copy 2. Item is in English.
  - Item 17: Labor Looks at Education, Publication (Box 1, Folder 20a)
    By Mark Starr. Copy 2. Item is in English.
  - Item 18: New Zealands Labor Government at Work, Publication (Box 1, Folder 20a)
    By W. B. Sutch. Copy 2. Item is in English.
  - Item 19: Workers Education Today, Publication (Box 1, Folder 20a)
  - Item 20: Workers Education Today, Publication (Box 1, Folder 20a)
    By Mark Starr. Copy 3. Item is in English.
- S [folder 2 of 2], Publication (Box 1, Folder 20b)
  - Item 1: Anti-Labor Activities in the United States, Publication (Box 1, Folder 20b)
  - Item 2: Sit-down; A. G. M. Stockholder Visits Flint, Publication (Box 1, Folder 20b)
  - Item 3: Shall Strikes Be Outlawed?, Publication (Box 1, Folder 20b)
  - Item 4: Mexico In Transition, Publication (Box 1, Folder 20b)
  - Item 5: What Is FolkSocialism? A Critical Analysis, Publication (Box 1, Folder 20b)
  - Item 6: The Intellectual And The Labor Movement, Publication (Box 1, Folder 20b)
  - Item 7: The Accumulation of Capital: Social vs. Personal Savings, Publication (Box 1, Folder 20b)
  - Item 8: Labor Looks at Education, Publication (Box 1, Folder 20b)
  - Item 9: Workers Education Today, Publication (Box 1, Folder 20b)
  - Item 10: New Zealands Labor Government at Work, Publication (Box 1, Folder 20b)
  - Item 11: Anti-Labor Activities in the United States, Publication (Box 1, Folder 20b)
  - Item 12: Anti-Labor Activities in the United States, Publication (Box 1, Folder 20b)
  - Item 13: Sit-down; A. G. M. Stockholder Visits Flint, Publication (Box 1, Folder 20b)
  - Item 14: Shall Strikes Be Outlawed?, Publication (Box 1, Folder 20b)
  - Item 15: Shall Strikes Be Outlawed?, Publication (Box 1, Folder 20b)
  - Item 16: What Is FolkSocialism? A Critical Analysis, Publication (Box 1, Folder 20b)
  - Item 17: Labor Looks at Education, Publication (Box 1, Folder 20b)
  - Item 18: New Zealands Labor Government at Work, Publication (Box 1, Folder 20b)
  - Item 19: Workers Education Today, Publication (Box 1, Folder 20b)
  - Item 20: Workers Education Today, Publication (Box 1, Folder 20b)
- T [folder 1 of 2], Publication (Box 2, Folder 1a)
  - Item 1: A Socialist Looks At The New Deal, Publication (Box 2, Folder 1a)
    By Norman Thomas. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Democracy Versus Dictatorship, Publication (Box 2, Folder 1a)
  - Item 3: Democratic Socialism: A New Appraisal, Publication (Box 2, Folder 1a)
  - Item 4: Russia Democracy or Dictatorship, Publication (Box 2, Folder 1a)
    By Norman Thomas; Joel Seidman. Item is in English.
  - Item 5: The Challenge of War: An Economic Interpretation, Publication (Box 2, Folder 1a)
  - Item 6: The Challenge of War: An Economic Interpretation, Publication (Box 2, Folder 1a)
    By Norman Thomas. revised. Item is in English.
  - Item 7: the Plight of the Share-Cropper, Publication (Box 2, Folder 1a)
    By Norman Thomas. Includes a Report of Survey made by the Memphis Chapter, L. I. D. and the Tyronza Socialist Party under the direction of William R. Amberson. Item is in English.
  - Item 8: Russia Democracy or Dictatorship, Publication (Box 2, Folder 1a)
  - Item 9: War as A Socialist See It, Publication (Box 2, Folder 1a)
  - Item 10: What Is Industrial Democracy, Publication (Box 2, Folder 1a)
    By Norman Thomas. 8pp. Item is in English.
  - Item 11: What Is Industrial Democracy, Publication (Box 2, Folder 1a)
    By Norman Thomas. 59pp. Item is in English.
  - Item 12: Why I Am a Socialist, Publication (Box 2, Folder 1a)
  - Item 13: Twenty Years of Social Pioneering: L. I. D. 20th Anniversary, Publication (Box 2, Folder 1a)
  - Item 14: Twenty Years of Social Pioneering: L. I. D. 20th Anniversary, Publication (Box 2, Folder 1a)
  - Item 15: Democracy Versus Dictatorship, Publication (Box 2, Folder 1a)
    By Norman Thomas. Copy 2. Item is in English.
  - Item 16: Democratic Socialism: A New Appraisal, Publication (Box 2, Folder 1a)
  - Item 17: The Plight of the Share-Cropper, Publication (Box 2, Folder 1a)
    By Norman Thomas. Includes a Report of Survey made by the Memphis Chapter, L. I. D. and the Tyronza Socialist Party under the direction of William R. Amberson. Copy 2. Item is in English.
  - Item 18: A Socialist Looks At The New Deal, Publication (Box 2, Folder 1a)
  - Item 19: War as A Socialist See It, Publication (Box 2, Folder 1a)
  - Item 20: What Is Industrial Democracy, Publication (Box 2, Folder 1a)
    By Norman Thomas. 59pp. Copy 2. Item is in English.
  - Item 21: What Is Industrial Democracy, Publication (Box 2, Folder 1a)
    By Norman Thomas. 8pp. Copy 2. Item is in English.
  - Item 22: Why I Am a Socialist, Publication (Box 2, Folder 1a)
- T [folder 2 of 2], Publication (Box 2, Folder 1b)
  - Item 1: A Socialist Looks At The New Deal, Publication (Box 2, Folder 1b)
  - Item 2: Democracy Versus Dictatorship, Publication (Box 2, Folder 1b)
  - Item 3: Democratic Socialism: A New Appraisal, Publication (Box 2, Folder 1b)
  - Item 4: Russia Democracy or Dictatorship, Publication (Box 2, Folder 1b)
  - Item 5: The Challenge of War: An Economic Interpretation, Publication (Box 2, Folder 1b)
  - Item 6: The Challenge of War: An Economic Interpretation, Publication (Box 2, Folder 1b)
  - Item 7: the Plight of the Share-Cropper, Publication (Box 2, Folder 1b)
  - Item 8: Russia Democracy or Dictatorship, Publication (Box 2, Folder 1b)
  - Item 9: War as A Socialist See It, Publication (Box 2, Folder 1b)
  - Item 10: What Is Industrial Democracy, Publication (Box 2, Folder 1b)
  - Item 11: What Is Industrial Democracy, Publication (Box 2, Folder 1b)
  - Item 12: Why I Am a Socialist, Publication (Box 2, Folder 1b)
  - Item 13: Twenty Years of Social Pioneering: L. I. D. 20th Anniversary, Publication (Box 2, Folder 1b)
  - Item 14: Twenty Years of Social Pioneering: L. I. D. 20th Anniversary, Publication (Box 2, Folder 1b)
  - Item 15: Democracy Versus Dictatorship, Publication (Box 2, Folder 1b)
  - Item 16: Democratic Socialism: A New Appraisal, Publication (Box 2, Folder 1b)
  - Item 17: The Plight of the Share-Cropper, Publication (Box 2, Folder 1b)
  - Item 18: A Socialist Looks At The New Deal, Publication (Box 2, Folder 1b)
  - Item 19: War as A Socialist See It, Publication (Box 2, Folder 1b)
  - Item 20: What Is Industrial Democracy, Publication (Box 2, Folder 1b)
  - Item 21: What Is Industrial Democracy, Publication (Box 2, Folder 1b)
  - Item 22: Why I Am a Socialist, Publication (Box 2, Folder 1b)
- U, Publication (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: The Unemployed: L. I. D., Publication (Box 2, Folder 2)
    By League for Industrial Democracy (LID). no.1 (1930: Dec.). Item is in English.
  - Item 2: The Unemployed: L. I. D., Publication (Box 2, Folder 2)
    By League for Industrial Democracy (LID). no.2 (1931, Feb.). Item is in English.
  - Item 3: The Unemployed: L. I. D., Publication (Box 2, Folder 2)
    By League for Industrial Democracy (LID). no.3 (1931: Spring). Item is in English.
  - Item 4: The Unemployed: L. I. D., Publication (Box 2, Folder 2)
    By League for Industrial Democracy (LID). no.4. Item is in English.
- V, Publication (Box 2, Folder 3)
- W, Publication (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: The Profit Motive: Is It Indispensable To Industry, Publication (Box 2, Folder 4)
    By Harry F. Ward. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: The L. I. D.: Fifty Years of Democratic Education, 1905-1955, Publication (Box 2, Folder 4)
    By Mina Weisenburg. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: Industrial Unionism In the American Labor Movement, Publication (Box 2, Folder 4)
    By Theresa Wolfson; Abraham Weiss. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: The L. I. D.: Fifty Years of Democratic Education, 1905-1955, Publication (Box 2, Folder 4)
    By Mina Weisenberg. Copy 2. Item is in English.
  - Item 5: Industrial Unionism In the American Labor Movement, Publication (Box 2, Folder 4)
    By Theresa Wolfson; Abraham Weiss. Copy 2. Item is in English.
  - Item 6: The Profit Motive: Is It Indispensable To Industry, Publication (Box 2, Folder 4)
    By Harry F. Ward. Third Printing. Item is in English.
  - Item 7: Public Debt and Taxation in the Postwar World, Publication (Box 2, Folder 4)
    By William Withers. Item is in English.
- XYZ, Publication (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: U. S. A.: A Blueprint of Fair Competition, Publication (Box 2, Folder 5)
    By Charles N. Young. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: A Course in Socialism, Publication (Box 2, Folder 5)
    By Jesse Lynch Williams. Item is in English.
- Other, Publication (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: Forty Years of Education: A symposium, Publication (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Item 2: Thirtieth Anniversary Report, 1905-1935, Publication (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Item 3: What is the L. I. D., Publication (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Item 4: Students in Revolt: The Story of the Intercollegiate League for Industrial Democracy, Publication (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Item 5: L. I. D. News Letter: Annual Report for 1935, Publication (Box 2, Folder 6)
    By League for Industrial Democracy (LID). February 15, 1936. Item is in English.
  - Item 6: L. I. D. Study Commissions General Bulletin, Publication (Box 2, Folder 6)
    By League for Industrial Democracy (LID). no.1. Item is in English.
  - Item 7: L. I. D. Study Commissions General Bulletin, Publication (Box 2, Folder 6)
    By League for Industrial Democracy (LID). no.3. Youth and the Social Order. Item is in English.
  - Item 8: L. I. D. Study Commissions General Bulletin, Publication (Box 2, Folder 6)
    By League for Industrial Democracy (LID). no.4. The Legacy of John Dewey. Item is in English.